♪ You could see that Pierre
♪ Did truly love
the mademoiselle ♪
♪ And now
the young monsieur... ♪
(Penny:)Inevitable, you say?
(Leonard:)I'll just let my hips
do the talkin'.
♪ It goes to show
you never can tell... ♪
(Howard:)Screw it. I'm calling
and finding out.
(Bernadette:)Good. Call him.
(Bernadette:)Wait, I'm not sure
I want to know.
(Howard:)But you just said
you wanted to know.
(Bernadette:)Well, now I don't know
if I want to know!
(Raj:)Hello?
(Howard:)Call you back.
(Sheldon:)No, Dr. Feynman.
(Sheldon:)If I solve it for you,
you'll never learn.
♪ Tootsee Roll
♪ Tootsee
Roll ♪
♪ Tootsee Roll,
Tootsee Roll... ♪
Wow! Where did you
learn these moves?
(Leonard:)The world may have forgotten
about Dance Dance Revolution,
(Leonard:)but not this smooth criminal.